Leonard Carmichael Papers ca.1917-1973 Mss.B.C212
American Philosophical Society
- Leonard Carmichael Papers, ca. 1917-1973 (Box 1)
  - Hague Conference Miscellaneous After Signing of Treaty
    - Martin, Elvira P
    - Foley, John
    - Van der Haagen, J K
    - Crosby, Sumner McKnight
    - Rohling, F P Th
    - Andrews, Mrs. Joseph J
    - Salter, L J
    - Donhauser, Robert
    - McCardle, Carl W
  - Hague Conference Miscellaneous Comments on Draft of Treaty
    - Cunliffe, A W
  - Hague Conference Miscellaneous Prior to Signing of Treaty
    - Graf, J E
    - McCardle, Carl W
    - Bantung, J P
  - Hague Conference - Newspaper Articles
    - Davis, Watson
    - Van de Water, Marjorie
  - Hague Conference - Outline of U.S. Gov't Activities and Measures for the Internat'l Protection of Cultural Institutions
  - Hague Conference - Publications on Protection of Cultural Property
    - Wilhelm, Rene-Jean
  - Hague Conference - Report for State Department
    - Martin, Elvira P
  - Hague Conference - Treaty Correspondence
    - Van Der Haagen, J K
    - Isenbergh, Max
    - Nitze, Paul H
    - Gates, Thomas S, Jr.
    - Thayer, Robert H
  - Hague Conference - Typical State Department Reports on Internat'l Conferences
  - Hague Conference - UNESCO Newsletters
  - Hague Conference - U.S.S.R. Ratifies Treaty
  - Hague Conference - Vedovato, "International Protection of Historical Monuments Against Air Bombardment"
  - Hague Conference
    - Hay, John
    - Gates, Thomas S, Jr.
    - Cairns, Huntington
    - Mithoefer, William C, Jr.
    - Quarles, Donald A
    - McElroy, Neil
    - Roche, Maurice W
    - McCardle, Carl W
    - Dulles, John Foster
    - Crosby, Sumner
    - Weislogel, Winifred S
  - Hahn, Emily
  - Haider
  - Hainer, Gwendolyn
  - Haines, Laura
  - Haines, Preston B
  - Haines, R F
  - Haislip, Wade H
  - Hale, Whitney
  - Hall, Calvin S
  - Hall, E Raymond
  - Hall of Fame Committee
    - Stevens, John Frank
    - Wisely, William H
    - Rosenhaus, Matthew B
    - Whaler, James
    - Payne, M M
    - Wetmore, Alexander
    - Prince, Gregory
  - Halsted, David C
  - Hall, George D
  - Hall, Joyce C
  - Hall, K R L
  - Hall, Richard L
  - Halley, Rudolph
  - Hallmark Cards
  - Halsey, James H
  - Halsey, Stuart and Company
  - Halsted Press
  - Halverson, H M
  - Hamarneh, Sami K
  - Hamarneh, Sami K
    - Ruth, Joseph Y
    - Murshed, Raja D
  - Hamburger, Viktor
  - Hamer, Robert C
  - Hamill, Ruth
  - Hamilton, George E, Jr.
  - Hammona, Linda
  - Hammond, Paul
  - Hammond, William C, Jr.
  - Hampton, Howard A
  - Hancock, Elliott
  - Hancock, John - Mutual Life Insurance Co.
  - Hancock, Walker
  - Handler, Philip
  - Handling of Technical Personnel in Germany, 1944 May 1
  - Handy, Grace
  - Haney, Charles A
  - Hanford, H Merle
    - MacLean, Basil C
  - Hanify, Edward B
  - Hannah, John A
    - Bronk, Detlev W
  - Hanney, George W
  - Hansen, Christopher S
  - Hansen, Oskar III
  - Hanson, Arthur W
  - Hanson, Elisha
  - Hanson, F Charles
  - Hanson, Hanson and Cobb
    - Hanson, Arthur B
    - Huber, Joseph
  - Hanson, Kurtz M
  - Harbeson, John
  - Harcourt, Brace and Company
  - Harden, Carl
  - Harden, Luberta M
  - Hardin, Richard B
  - Hardy, Gelston
  - Hardy, Martha C
  - Hargrett, Lester
  - Harley, Harrison L
  - Harlow, Harry F
  - Harmon, George H
  - Harmon, John M
  - Harms, Ernest
  - Harper Brothers
    - MacGregor, Frank S
  - Harper, Debbie
    - Harper, John C
    - Rogers, James H
    - Hornig, Donald F
    - Hallowell, Burton C
  - Harper, Jeff
  - Harper, Robert G
  - Harrell, Joe E
  - Harrell, Linwood P
  - Harrell, Thomas W
    - Edwards, A S
  - Harrington, Arthur H
  - Harrington, E Viola
  - Harrington, Joyce
    - Whitmore, Frank C, Jr.
  - Harrington, Milton
  - Harris, A E
  - Harris, Albert J
  - Harris, John D
  - Harris, Frederick Brown
  - Harris, J Donald
  - Harris, L James
  - Harris, Norman D
  - Harris, Roger
  - Harris, Rufus Carrollton
  - Harris, Seymour
  - Harris, Walter D
  - Harrison, Carter
  - Harrison, David R
  - Harrison, E C
  - Harrison, James S
  - Harrison, Laurence
    - Walker, John
    - Helson, Harry
  - Harrison, Lloyd
  - Harrison, Richard Edes
    - Mead, Leonard
  - Harrison, Ross G
  - Harrower, Mary R
  - Harrower, Molly
  - Harrub, Deborah H
  - Harter, Karl W
  - Harter, Richard S
  - Hartford Retreat, Neuro-Psychiatric Institute of
  - Hartke, Gilbert V, O.P.
    - Orsinger, Victor J
  - Hartley, Robert W
  - Hartline, Elizabeth Kraus
  - Hartman, C G
  - Hartmann, George W
  - Hartshorne, Charles
  - Hartson, L D
  - Hartzog, George B
  - Harvard Apparatus Company
  - Harvard Club of Washington, D. C.
    - McGrath, Joseph
    - Hayes, Patrick
    - Lee, Frederick B
    - Wainscott, Ann
    - Castle, William R
    - Luneta, Vincent N
    - Clark, Henry W
    - Rabb, Maxwell M
    - Fisher, Martin T
    - Kavanagh, E C
  - Harvard Cooperative Society
  - Harvard Foundation, 1951-53
    - Huggins, Gordon
    - Wulsin, Lucien
    - Walker, John
    - Danielian, Noobar R
    - Perkins, Dexter
  - Harvard Foundation - Address Lists
    - Huggins, Gordon
  - Harvard Foundation - Council Meetings
    - Wilson, Orme
    - Pei, Ieoh Ming
    - Rawson, Robert H
    - Litchfield, Lawrence, Jr.
    - Wulsin, Lucien, Sr.
  - Harvard Foundation - Financial Correspondence
  - Harvard Foundation - General
    - Huggins, Gordon
    - Ford, Franklin
    - Sawyer, John E
    - Lewis, Deming
    - Glosser, Mary D
    - Hanson, Arthur
    - Forbes, Alexander C
    - Dunaway, Don Carlos
    - Kevorkian, Hagop
    - Minasian, Ralph D
    - Collado, Emilio G
    - Hickman, R W
    - Perkins, Dexter
  - Harvard Foundation Council
    - Dromey, John A
    - Huggins, Gordon
    - Wells, A J
    - Johnson, Joseph E
  - Harvard Foundation - General
    - Theodorides, Phrixos J
    - Houghteling, James Lawrence, Jr.
    - Bauer, Mrs. G Philip
    - Danielian, N R
    - Sloan, A W
    - Sweetser, Arthur
    - Cater, S Douglass
    - Grew, Joseph C
    - Blake, Thomas D
    - Walker, John 3rd
    - Anastos, Milton V
    - Keiser, George Camp
    - Wilson, Orme
    - Breckenridge, F C
    - Land, William G
    - Oioem Higb
    - Winslow, E M
    - Mason, Charles Noble, Jr.
    - Davison, Roderic H
    - Sweetser, Arthur
    - Clapp, Verner Warren
    - Wrather, W E
    - Bundy, McGeorge
    - Munro, Mary F
    - Nitze, Paul H
    - Grew, Joseph C
  - Harvard Foundation - Minutes of Meetings
    - Perkins, Dexter
    - Huggins, Cordon
  - Harvard Foundation -- Middle Eastern Studies
  - Harvard University -- General
    - Biok, Derek C
    - Mattson, Hedy
    - Goodof, Paul S
    - Chapin, Aldus H
    - Steiner, Daniel
    - Hoguet, Robert L
    - Elkins, Kimball C
    - Pusey, Nathan M
    - Cardner, Robert
    - Caldwell, Ann W
    - Sprague, Wallace A
    - Gillette, Howard F
    - Rothschild, Walter N, Jr.
    - Dromey, John A
    - Cohen, Joel E
    - Brower, Reuben A
    - Trottenberg, A D
    - Ford, Franklin L
    - Huggins, Gordon
    - Amory, Robert Jr.
    - Miller, Samuel H
  - Harvard Summer School, 1928-31
    - Bishop, Dorcas N
    - Gill, R C
    - Burggraaf, Stanley
  - Harvard Tercentenary Conference
  - Harvard Univ. -- Ad hoc Committee on Psychology
    - Jenkins, H M
    - Miller, George A
    - Green, Bert F, Jr.
    - Torgerson, Warren S
    - Stevens, S S
    - Herrnstein, R J
    - Ekman, Gosta
    - McClelland, David C
    - White, Robert W
    - Ford, Franklin L
    - Kagan, Jerome
    - Abelson, Robert P
    - Brown, Roger
    - Pusey, Nathan M
  - Harvard University - Board of Overseers
    - Gillette, Howard F
    - Rothschild, Walter N, Jr.
    - Pusey, Nathan M
    - Parker, Augustin H
    - Pratt, H Irving
    - Mayr, Ernst
    - Davis, Nathanael V
    - Newman, Edwin B
  - Harvard University Dept. of Psychology
    - Gleason, Lucille
    - Allport, Gordon
    - Boring, Edwin G
  - Harvard Film Service
  - Harvard University
  - Harvard - Ad Hock Committee on Astronomy
    - Pusey, Nathan H
    - Menzel, Donald H
    - Payne-Gaposchkin, Cecilia
    - Bundy, McGeorge
    - Carrier, George
  - Harvard - Ad Hock Committee on Biology
    - Buck, Paul H
    - Thimann, Kenneth V
    - Castle, Edward S
    - Redfield, Alfred C
    - Lashley, K S
    - Miller, Alden H
    - Pitelka, Frank A
    - Romer, Alfred S
    - Scholander, P F
    - Bates, Marston
    - Bethe, H A
    - Boring, Edwin G
    - Holtfreter, J
    - Frisch, K V
    - Conant, James B
    - Vowles, David
    - Mangelsdorf, Paul C
    - Conant, James
    - Gillette, Howard F
    - Shultz, Peter D
    - Perkins, Roswell B
  - Harvard Alumni Association
    - Perkins, Roswell B
    - Gillette, Howard F
    - Huggins, Gordon
    - Pratt, Albert
    - Shultz, Peter D
    - Cutter, R Ammi
  - Harvard -- Boston University Extension Courses
    - Mahoney, John J
    - Kimball, Ethel
  - Harvard -- Center for Cognitive Studies
    - Miller, George A
  - Harvard Commission: 25 yrs. later
    - Appley, M H
  - Harvard General
    - Pusey, Nathan M
    - Huggins, Gordon
    - Hanfmann, George M A
    - Gores, Harold B
    - Amory, Robert, Jr.
    - Jackson, William A
    - Brooks, Howard L
    - Lund, Charles C
    - Burton, William H
    - Greene, Mrs. John A
    - Mann, W M
    - Gilbert, Carl J
    - Van Vleck, J H
    - Elliott, William Y
    - Shattuck, Henry L
  - Harvard Univ. (In honor of Charles William Eliot)
  - Harvard Univ. (LL.D.)
    - Little, David M
    - Conant, James B
    - Cabot, Powell M
  - Harvard University - Overseers' Committee
    - Mayr, Ernst
    - Mallinckrodt, Laurence E
    - Davis, Nathanael V
    - White, Alexander M
    - Howard, John K
    - Smith, A C
    - Dana, Richard H
    - Romer, Alfred S
    - Rockefeller, David
    - Terry, Lawrence
    - Pratt, H Irving
    - Menzel, Donald H
    - Bailey, David W
    - Hallowell, John W
    - Pusey, Nathan M
    - Trottenberg, A D
    - Bundy, McGeorge
    - Piel, Gerard
    - Kuble, Lawrence S
    - Mallinckrodt, Laurence E
    - Stevens, S S
    - Black, Curtis E
    - Newman, Edwin B
    - Pool, J Lawrence
  - Harvester World
  - Harvey, O J
  - Hartwell Homestead
  - Harwell, Mrs. W B
  - Haselmayer, Louis A
  - Haskins, Caryl P
    - Leakey, Richard E
  - Hass, Arnold
  - Hassan, Gail
  - Hassell, R L
  - Hastings, W T
  - Hatch, Francis W
  - Hatch, Frank
  - Hatch, John Davis, Jr.
  - Hatt, Robert T
  - Hatter - Shirts, Shoes
  - Hauck, Arthur A
  - Haury, Emil W
  - Haussermann, Caroline
  - Haussermann, Oscar W
  - Haverlin, Carl
  - Hawaiian Botanical Gardens Foundation, Inc.
  - Hawkes, Clarence D
  - Hawkins, Gerald S
  - Hawley, Edmond G, Jr.
  - Hawley, Estelle
  - Hawley, John C
  - Hay, Carolynn
    - Snider, E
  - Hayaud-Din, M
  - Hayden, Philip Meserve
  - Hayden Planetarium
    - Branley, Franklyn M
  - Hayek, F A
  - Hayes, Keith J
  - Hayes, L Newton
  - Hayes, Samuel P
  - Hayman, Joseph M
  - Hayman, J M, Jr.
  - Haynes, Evelyn G
  - Hazard, Lauriston H
  - Hazen, Myron S
  - Health, Education and Welfare, Dept. of
    - Andervont, H B
  - Health General
  - Healy, William
  - Heap, George A
  - Hearne, John Joseph
  - Hebb,D O
  - Hechinger, John W
    - Hallowell, Burton C
  - Hecht Company
  - Hecker, Carolyn
  - Heckman, Ruth R
  - Heckschen, August
    - Paffrath, Leslie
  - Hedberg, Josephine T
  - Hediger, H
  - Hefferman, John B
  - Hegge, Thorleif G
  - Heiberg, Elvin R
  - Heidbreder, Edna
  - Heilmaier, Erich Paul
  - Heine, Albert
  - Heine, Cornelius
    - Bradley, James
  - Heinz, H J Company
  - Heiser, Florien
  - Heiser, Karl F
  - Helmholtz - Contributions to Psychology
  - Helms, Richard McGarrah
    - Fletcher, John
  - Helson, Harry
  - Hemingway, Franklin W
  - Hemisfair, 1968
    - Stevens, Marshall T
  - Henderson, Alfred R
  - Henderson, Courtney C
  - Henderson, Ernest
    - Henderson, Barclay
    - Avis, Fred
    - Sullivan, Richard H
    - Green, Earl L
    - Davis, Randall
    - Scott, Arthur F
  - Henderson, Herbert T
  - Henderson, J Raymond
  - Henderson, Mrs. Leland F
  - Henderson, Mary Louise
  - Henderson, Steuart
  - Henion, Ruth
    - Remmers, H B
  - Henle, Ray
  - Henmon, V A C
  - Hennage Creative Printers
  - Hennage, Joseph E
    - Penrose, Charles Jr.
    - Moe, Henry Allen
  - Hennessy, Timothy
  - Hennigar, Gordon R
  - Henny, Christine Y
    - Watson, Thomas J, Jr.
  - Henrich, Eileen
  - Henry, Joseph - House
  - Henry, Joseph - Scientific Genius
  - Henry, Thomas R
    - Ennis, Jean
  - Henshaw, Paul S
  - Henson, W R
  - Herber, Elmer C
  - Herbert, Thomas J
  - Heritage Foundation
    - Flynt, Henry N
  - Herman, David T
  - Hermann, Alfred
  - Herold, Marjorie
  - Heron, W T
  - Hernia Repair
    - Proger, Samuel
    - Broadbent, Sam R
    - Wenley, A G
  - Heron, William T
  - Herr, Elizabeth. Experimental Psychology
  - Herr, Jane
    - Bowman, J K
  - Herrick, C Judson
  - Herrington, B M
  - Herrman, Charles
  - Herrnstein, Richard "I.Q." Article, Atlantic
  - Herron, R E
  - Herron, Robert F
  - Herschman, Arthur
    - Bixler, Seelye
    - Trytten, M H
  - Hershey, Lewis B
    - Kossa, Frank R
  - Hertz
  - Herzog, Henry W
  - Hess, E H
  - Hess, Julius H
  - Hess, J M
  - Hetzler, Peg
  - Heusel, Mrs. R
  - Hewlett, Horace W
  - Hexter, J H
  - Hibbard, Walter H
  - Hickey, Mrs. Harry K
  - Hicks, Reginald
  - Higbee, Katharine
  - Higgins, John W
  - Higgins, Mary F
  - Higginson, Glenn D
  - Highet, Gilbert A
  - Hightower, Jim
  - Highway Users Federation
  - Hildemann, W H
  - Hildreth, Harold M
  - Hildreth, Jane
    - Roberts, S O
  - Hilgard, Ernest R
  - Hilger, M Inez
    - Smith, Mary Griswold
    - Osendorf, Henrita
    - Idzerda, Stanley J
    - Merrick, Toni
    - Wilburn, Herbert S, Jr.
    - Chapnick, Howard
    - Murphy, Charlene L
  - Hill, David S
  - Hill, John E
  - Hill, John W
  - Hill, Robert W
  - Hill, Ruth
  - Hill, Susan
  - Hilsee, Donald A
  - Hilton, Barron
  - Hilton, Esther M
  - Hinckley, E D
  - Hindle, Charles F
  - Hines, George F
  - Hinkley, J W
    - Barker, J W
  - Hinrichs, A F
  - Hinsey, Joseph C
  - Hirsch, Jerry
  - Hirsch, Richard S
  - Hirshhorn Sculpture Garden
    - Clarke, Gilmore D
    - Nedzi, Lucien N
    - Ripley, S Dillon
  - Hirshson, Louis M
  - Hiscocks, E S
  - Hislop, Robert N
  - Historic Denver, Inc.
  - History of Psychology
  - Hites, Laird T
  - Hitz, Ralph
  - Hjortsjo, Carl-Herman
  - Hoag, J Paul
  - Hoagland, Edward
  - Hoagland, Hudson
    - Wall, Alexander J
  - Hobart Cabinet Company
  - Hobbs, Conrad
  - Hochberg, Lottie
  - Hocking, William Ernest
  - Hodges, Hamlin
  - Hodgman, William L
  - Hodgson, Corrin H
  - Hodnett, E
  - Hoelzel, Frederick
  - Hoemann, Maria
  - Hoes, Laurence Gouverneur
  - Hoffman, Arthur C The Reliability of the Changes in the Corneo-Retinal Potential Difference for Recording the Movements of the Eyes.
  - Hoffman, Danny
  - Hoffman, Irvin N
  - Hoftyzer, Ernest
  - Hogan, Bartholomew W
    - Saltonstall, Leverett
    - Martin, Joseph W, Jr.
    - Kennedy, John F
    - McCormack, John W
  - Hogan, Helen P
  - Hogan and Walter
  - Hogg, Ira D
  - Hoisington, Louis B
  - Holcomb, Louise
  - Holden, Rickey
    - Wessel, Nils Y
  - Holiday
    - Washburn, Ruth
  - Hollander, Edwin P
  - Hollingworth, H L
  - Hollister, Coburn D
  - Hollister, John
  - Holloway, James L, Jr.
  - Holmes, A W
  - Holmes, Henry Wyman
    - Cotton, Dana M
    - Mahoney, John J
  - Holmes, John
    - Clapp, Verner W
  - Holmes, John F
  - Holmes, Theta
    - Morriss, Margaret
    - Kline, Linus W
  - Holsopple, J Q
  - Holt, Edwin B
  - Holt, Henry and Co., Inc.
  - Holt, Kr
    - Boring, Edwin G
  - Holt, Rinehart and Winston, Inc.
  - Holton, Gerald
  - Holyoke, Edward
  - Holzer, Purl Edward
  - Homburger, Freddy
  - Homestead
  - Honeywell, Roy J
  - Honkavaara, Sylvia
  - Honorary Degrees
  - Honzik, C
  - Honzik, Marjorie P
  - Hooker, Davenport
    - Humphrey, Tryphena
    - Murchison, Carl
    - Barron, Donald H
    - Woodworth, Robert S
  - Hookway, H T
  - Hooper, Edwin B
  - Hoopingarner, N L
  - Hoover, J Edgar
  - Hopkins, Edward
  - Hopkinson, Edward, Jr.
  - Hopla, Cluff E
  - Hopper, Bruce C
  - Hopp, Gerhard
  - Hoppock, Robert
  - Hornbeck, Stanley K
  - Horne, Alexander
  - Horne, Mrs. Elwood O
  - Horne, Ralph W
  - Hornig, Chris
  - Hornung, Gertrude S
    - Cairns, Huntington
  - Horrocks, John E
  - Horstman, Robert
    - Starbird, Ethel A
  - Horton, Mrs. A F
  - Horton, B J
  - Horton, George P
  - Horton, J W
  - Horton, Warren
  - Horvitz, Harold
  - Hostetter, D Ralph
  - Hot Springs, Virginia
  - Hotaling, N L
  - Hotchkiss, S L
  - Hotel Bancroft
  - Hotel Taft
  - Hotel William Penn
  - Hottel, Martin P
  - Hough, Margaret Carter
    - Pope, Mrs. John A
    - Van Arsdale, Mrs. Dorothy T
  - Houghteling, James L
    - Hirshson, Louis M
    - Spaulding, William E
  - Houghton, Amory
  - Houghton Mifflin Company
    - Spaulding, William E
    - Millett, Ursula
    - Aldrich, Richard S
    - Hebert, Felix
    - Metcalf, Jesse Houghton
    - Morton, Sarah
    - Earle, Osborne
  - Houghton Mifflin Company - Arnheim
  - Houghton Mifflin Co. - Arnheim, Rudolf
    - Rooney, Robert C
  - Houghton Mifflin Co. - Austrin, H R
  - HMC Axline, Virginia M, DIES: In Search of Self
    - Rooney, Robert C
    - Brooks, Paul
    - Fuller, Henry R
    - McIcinney, Fred
    - Gibson, Diane
  - HMC Benda, Clemens E
  - HMC Biel, William C Psychology of Modern Human Engineering
  - HMC Book by Freud on W. Wilson
    - Rooney, Robert C
  - HMC Brozek, Josef - Revision of Warren Dictionary
    - Rooney, Robert C
  - HMC Buchwald and Peterson, "Abnormal Psychology"
    - Peterson, Donald R
    - Rooney, Robert C
    - Buchwald, Alexander M
  - HMC Calfee, Robert C
  - HMC Cameron's Personality Development and Psychopathology
    - Cameron, Norman
    - Fernald, L Dodge, Jr.
    - Rooney, Robert C
    - Furlong, Paul T
    - Tagiuri, Renato
    - Joyce, Hugh E, Jr.
    - Clark, Richard N
  - HMC Carmichael, Leonard Animal Infancy
    - Crook, Dorothea J
    - Rooney, Robert C
    - Reed, Theodore H
  - HMC Leonard Carmichael's Proposed Book on the History of Ideas
    - Rooney, Robert C
  - HMC Chomsky, Noam Language and Mind
    - Rooney, Robert C
  - HMC William C. Cobb
    - Egbert, Robert L
    - Thompson, George G
    - Clark, Richard N, Jr.
    - Pratt, Carroll C
    - Gumm, B L
    - MacMillan, John W
    - Jenness, Arthur F
    - Pierce, Marvin
    - Herring, Pendleton
  - HMC Crawford, Meredith Psychology of Training
    - McGinnies, Elliott
  - HMC Crook, Dr. Dorothea J
    - Rooney, Robert C
  - HMC Daniel, Robert S Electroencephalography and Behavior
  - HMC Daniel, Robert S Introductory Psychology
    - Rooney, Robert C
  - HMC Davis, Dr. John
    - Miller, Neal E
    - Rooney, Robert C
  - HMC Engen, Trygg General Psychology 5th Ed.
    - Rooney, Robert C
    - Kling, Julius
  - HMC Feldstone, Charles S
    - Rooney, Robert C
  - HMC Ferster and McGinnies
    - McGinnies, Elliott
    - Quigley, John H
    - Ferster, Charles B
    - Rooney, Robert
  - HMC Fitts, Paul
    - Rooney, Robert C
    - Poindexter, John W
    - Grant, Stephen W
    - Alexander, Theron
  - HMC General
    - Rooney, Robert C
    - Rogers, Carl R
    - Richter, Anders
    - Mischel, Walter
    - Ringness, Thomas A
    - Lowe, Douglas M
    - Maier, Norman R F
    - Barton, Anthony
    - Tomlinson, T M
    - Icrawiec, T S
    - Kessen
    - Holloway, Roger T
    - Ives, David O
    - Schultz, Duane P
    - Hammes, John A
    - Grant, Stephen W
    - Swan, Janet
    - Simkins, Lawrence
    - Munn, Norman
    - Poindexter, John W
    - Ahmavaara, Yrjo
    - Montagu, Ashley
    - Cranny, Charles J
    - Shemberg, Kenneth
    - Doherty, Michael E
    - Solem, Allen R
    - Krawiec, Theophile S
    - Gibson, James J
    - Draguns, Juris G
    - McCurdy, Harold G
    - Chapin, Priscilla E
    - Knapp, Robert H
    - Lehner, George
    - Pfaffman, Carl
    - Bartley, S Howard
    - Zangwill, O L
    - Jaynes, Julian
    - Leuba, Clarence
    - Ulrich, Roger E
    - Rich, Philip
    - Bussey, Ruth Cruikshank
    - Johnson, Robert
    - Jenness, Richard C
    - Anderson, D Chris
    - Borkowsky, John
    - Cooper, Les
    - Fernald, L Dodge, Jr.
    - Munn, Norman
    - Gibson, James J
    - Csikszentmihaly, Mihaly
    - Thoma, Henry F
    - Cobb, William C
    - Wiles, Eleanor
    - Clark, Richard N
    - Gough, Harrison G
    - Scott, J P
    - Kappauf, William E
    - Patterson, C H
    - Mowrer, O Hobart
    - Engle, T L
    - MacKinnon, Donald W
    - Fisher, Granville C
    - Sarbin, Theodore R
    - Stacey, Chalmers L
    - Cofer, Charles N
    - Spaulding, William E
    - Ackley, Gardner
    - Roesch, Raymond A
    - Morin, Alexander J
    - Munn, Norman L
    - Bitterman, M E
    - Postman, Leo
  - HMC Gibson, Eleanor J
    - Rooney, Robert C
    - MacDonald, William D
  - HMC Gibson, James Revision of Visual World and The Senses
    - Rooney, Robert C
    - Gibson, James J
    - Faissler, Diane
  - HMC Gibson, Mrs. James J Book on Perceptua Learning
    - Rooney, Robert C
  - HMC Goldfried, Marvin, Special Applications of the Rorschach
    - Rooney, Robert C
    - Reger, Roger
    - Dashiell, John F
  - HMC Grant, Stephen W
    - Hamilton, Elizabeth V
    - Clark, Richard N, Jr.
    - Munn, Norman L
    - Clark, Richard N, Jr.
    - Newman, Edwin B
    - Glock, Marvin D
    - MacMillan, J W
    - Spaulding, William E
    - Harrison, Carter
    - Thoma, Henry F
    - Land, Edwin H
    - Helson, Harry
    - Garmezy, Norman
    - Daniel, Roger S
    - English, Horace B
    - Pratt, Carroll C
    - Burke, Thelma
    - Mowrer, O Hobart
    - Thompson, Helen
    - Hunt, Herold C
    - Maier, Norman R F
    - Seidman, Jerome M
  - HMC Green, Helen The Black Life Style
    - Knapp, Robert H
    - McCauley, Gerald
  - HMC Halcomb, C and Cross, H Contemporary Experimental Psychology
  - HMC Hart and Tomlinson's New Directions in
    - Client Centered Therapy
    - Hart, Joe T
    - Rooney, Robert C
    - Tomlinson, T M
  - HMC Hoffman, Arthur
  - HMC Horrocks, John E
  - HMC Horrocks, John Adolescence
    - Rooney, Robert C
  - HMC Horrocks, John International Series in the Behavioral Sciences
    - Marx, Melvin H
    - Lawson, C A
    - Rooney, Robert C
    - Alexander, Sir William
    - Hsu, Francis L K
    - Oleron, Pierre
    - Kardiner, A
    - Klopfer, Bruno
    - Reitan, Ralph M
    - Baker, Lawrence M
    - Barker, Roger G
    - Cameron, Norman
    - Fromm, Erich
    - Halstead, Ward C
    - Havighurst, Robert J
    - Montagu, Ashley
  - HMC Horrocks, John E Self and Role
    - Quigley, John H
  - HMC Introduction to Marvin D. Glock's Improvement of College Reading
    - Wiles, Eleanor
    - Thomas, Henry F
  - HMC Intro. to Thomas Gordon's Group-Centered Leadership
    - Grant, Stephen
  - HMC Intro. to Norman R.F. Maier's Psychology in Industry
    - Grant, Stephen W
  - HMC Intro. to Norman Munn's The Evolution and Growth of Human Behavior
    - Grant, Stephen
  - HMC Intro. to Jerome M. Seidman's Educational Psychology
    - Clark, Richard N, Jr.
  - HMC Koppenaal, Richard Text in General Introductory Psychology
    - Rooney, Robert C
  - HMC Lockhart, Russell A
    - Rooney, Robert C
  - HMC Luminaries
    - Rooney, Robert C
    - Brown, Roger W
    - Herrnstein, R J
    - Luce, R Duncan
    - Pettigrew, Thomas F
    - Logan, Frank A
    - Simon, Herbert A
    - Olds, James
  - HMC Maas, James B
  - HMC Manuscript Suggestions
    - Ferster, C B
    - McGinnies, Elliott
    - Quigley, John H
    - Rooney, Robert
    - Faissler, Diane
    - Munn, Norman L
    - Engen, Trygg
    - Melzack, Ronald
    - Johnson, Roger N
    - Horrocks, John E
    - Beach, Lee Roy
    - Pfaffmann, Carl
    - Bussey, Ruth C
    - Cameron, Norman A
    - Coons, Edgar E, Jr.
    - Ferster, Charles B
    - Levenway, Russell W
  - HMC Levinson's Patienthood in the Mental Hospital
    - Rooney, Robert C